<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>

<!-- 	<string id="st_not_in_use">
        <text>ѕредмет не используетс€/The Item is not in use (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_not_in_use_descr">
        <text>ѕредмет не используетс€/The Item is not in use </text>
    </string> -->

	<string id="st_knifebf4">
        <text>The ЂOTs-04ї Combat knife (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_knifebf4_descr">
        <text>The OTs-04 knife was developed at the Tula Central Design Research Bureau (TsKIB) in the late 80s - early 90s and was intended for special forces of the Interior Ministry troops.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_kukri">
        <text>Kukri (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_kukri_descr">
        <text>This is a special blade made of high-carbon spring-spring steel of the bus, which for many years stood in an anomalous field, and therefore has excellent cutting and chopping properties. Ideal for cutting mutants of all stripes, and for protection against them.</text>
		</string>

	<string id="st_tactical_knife">
		<text>Monolith's Blade (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tactical_knife_descr">
		<text>[RUSSIAN ACCENT "ON"] It is rumoured, these blades are produced in very a few by masters from a groupment Monolith. Threw composition of alloy not known - it is talked to extract him it is possible only in the heart of sarcophagus.[RUSSIAN ACCENT "OFF"]</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_tomahawk">
		<text>Gerber Downrange Tomahawk (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tomahawk_descr">
		<text>Tactical tomahawk, multi-tool and breaching tool, all-in-one solution.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 CQB (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration (military green colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup 5.56mm assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH&Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch). The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr "universal army rifle") was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units. CQB - has less weight and increased rate of fire compared to the original.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3 Commando (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - Army Universal Rifle) is an Austrian 5.56x45mm NATO bullpup assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr-Daimler-Puch and now manufactured by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG. The Steyr AUG A3 differs from the base model in the presence of four Picatinny slats: the top one is used for attaching sights, a grenade launcher or a vertical front handle can be attached to the bottom, and a laser pointer or other necessary additional equipment is attached to the side.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Trijicon Acog (x4) and PEQ LA5 LAM.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_howa20">
		<text>Howa Type 20 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_howa20_descr">
		<text>The assault rifle was officially unveiled to the public in May 2020. This weapon is intended to replace the Type 89 assault rifle, which has been in service for about 30 years. The new rifle of the Japanese Self-Defense Forces, like the previous one, was developed by Howa Machinery Co, and uses 5.56 mm ammunition. The development of a new rifle to replace the Type 89 began at the request of the Japanese Armed Forces in 2014. Externally and structurally, the new Type 20 rifle is a kind of arithmetic mean of many modern rifles, such as the HK433 or CZ BREN II, and, apparently, does not have any original features. However, there is nothing wrong with this, since it is not the originality of the design that is required from the army weapon, but reliability, low price and compliance with the customer's requirements. It remains a mystery how and in what quantity this rifle came to the participants of a scientific expedition to the Zone.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Includes: MARCH Shorty scope and AN/PEQ-15A DBAL-A2 Laser Device\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556">
		<text>Ruger SR-556 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_descr">
		<text>Several of these rifles entered the Zone through scientists. According to legend, Professor Sakharov received 6 small containers with these guns from foreign sponsors, but 5 of them were lost during transportation. Ruger SR-556 is an American self-loading carbine manufactured by the arms company Sturm, Ruger & Company, Inc. became the first Ruger of the AR-10 family. Ruger SR-762 chambered for .308. Belongs to a few samples of AR-15 rifles using the removal of powder gases. Production ceased in January 2016 after the introduction of the Keymod Lightweight option.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas">
		<text>MP-133 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas_descr">
		<text>The MP-133 is a product of the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant. This shotgun is an evolution of the earlier IZh-81 pump action shotgun, and is intended for civilian and security markets. It is produced in two basic versions: standard MP-133 with tubular magazine and MP-133K with detachable box magazine, both versions can be in various barrel lengths and styles, wood or polymer furniture, fixed or side folding polymer stock or pistol grip only. The MP-133 shotgun uses traditional pump action with sliding forend that has dual action bars. Locking is achieved by a tilting locking piece, installed in the bolt and engages the notch in the barrel extension when in battery. Feed is from tubular under-barrel magazine that holds 4 rounds, though capacity can be enhanced by installing magazine extension tubes.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas">
		<text>MP-153 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas_descr">
		<text>The MP-153 self-loading shotgun was the first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by Izhevsk Mechanical Plant. It was developed along with the pump action MP-133 shotgun and shares many parts and assemblies with it. The MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin, and is widely used to hunt various games in Russia. It is also sold for export, it is known as Remington "Spartan" SPR-453 autoloader in US. MP-153 shotguns are known for solid but somewhat heavy construction and reliability.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS: Specialized weapon mod kit</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1">
        <text>Carabineer (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1_descr">
		<text>A customized version of the MP-153 shotgun. Capable of semi-automatic fire like its predecessor, but provides better recoil compensation thanks to the quite effective muzzle brake. It also has Picatinny rail which allows to use reflex and holographic sights and ability to use sound suppressor.\n
	    %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Due to the position of the stock, it is possible to install sights only with a very low mount: Barska AC10632, C-More, Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1, Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, OKP-7, 1P76 Rakurs. \n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-1 suppressor</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber">
		<text>FN SCAR-H (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: FN HERSTAL FN40GL Mk2\n</text>
	</string>

<!-- 	<string id="st_wpn_scar_l_tac">
		<text>Scar-L CQB (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_l_tac_descr">
		<text>The FN SCAR-L (Special Operation Forces Combat Assault Rifle - Light) assault rifle chambered in 5.56x45 NATO rounds, was adopted by USSOCOM (United States Special Operations Command) as the Mk 16. Features a side-folding polymer stock and a free-floating, cold hammer-forged Mil-Spec barrel with hardchromed bore. Fully-ambidextrous operating controls instantly adapt the SCAR to any user or any shooting position. The receiver-integrated optical rail plus three accessory rails enable mounting of a wide variety of scopes, electronic sights, tactical lights and lasers. Manufactured by Fabrique Nationale Herstal. Comes in black and flat dark earth.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver, B.E. MEYERS MAWL-C1 tactical green laser aim modul (included) \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string> -->

	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_tac_siber">
		<text>SIG SG550 Tactical (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_tac_siber_descr">
		<text>Renowned for its high production quality and good performance, the SG 550 is often referred to as the finest 5.56 mm rifle ever made. It has a side-folding skeletonised buttstock and a lightweight aluminium bipod that folds into grooves in the lower handguard.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
	    %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Tactical handguard, Vertical grip, AN/PEQ-16 Laser Aim modul and Tritium sights.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight and 1P76 Rakurs (picatinny).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor\n
	    %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_tac_siber">
		<text>SIG SG552 Tac Commando (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_tac_siber_descr">
		<text>The SG 552 Commando is designed for urban combat, making it the most compact member of SIG's renowned SG 550 family, which enhances its CQC capabilities.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
	    %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Vertical grip, AN/PEQ-16 Laser Aim modul and Tritium sights.\n 		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight and 1P76 Rakurs (picatinny).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usp_tac">
        <text>HK USP Match Tactical (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_tac_descr">
        <text>This is a modification of the HK USP Match specially developed for scientists by the personal order of Professor Sakhorov, designed for use in the "Specialist-Scientist" kit. The operation of the system of mechanisms is improved with the help of artifacts. The difference from the standard USP Match is the ability to install a silencer. The gun is equipped with an enlarged magazine for 22 rounds of 9mm caliber. (The Specialist-Scientist kit includes: BCC Savant, HK USP Match Tactical, Monolith Blade).\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The kit includes Laser Aiming Module and Red Dot Sights mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Gemtech suppressor</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_grenade_launcher">
		<text>GP-25 "Kostyor" grenade launcher (BaS+Van)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_descr">
		<text>A single shot, front loaded, rifled under-barrel grenade launcher for assault rifles made in Warsaw Pact countries. Designed to greatly expand fire-power of a basic infantry squad. The firing mechanism is self-cocking, with a manual safety catch and automatic shot prevention if incorrectly installed onto a rifle.\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] muzzle velocity: %c[ui_gray_1]~76 m / sec\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] fire range: %c[ui_gray_1]~300 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] reload time: %c[ui_gray_1]slow\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ammunition: %c[ui_gray_1]VOG-25 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203">
		<text>M203 grenade launcher (BaS+Van)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203_descr">
		<text>A modified M203 grenade launcher whose length has been decreased by three inches, and which can be attached to weapons by means of a Picatinny rail. Thanks to a changed mount, this grenade launcher is widely used around the world and can be installed on most currently produced rifles. Although of more modern design, it has almost the same properties as its Soviet counterpart - the GP-25 grenade launcher.\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] muzzle velocity: %c[ui_gray_1]~76 m / sec\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] fire range: %c[ui_gray_1]~300 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] reload time: %c[ui_gray_1]slow\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ammunition: %c[ui_gray_1]M203 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
