<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
<!-- 	<string id="st_not_in_use">
        <text>ѕредмет не используетс€/The Item is not in use (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_not_in_use_descr">
        <text>ѕредмет не используетс€/The Item is not in use </text>
    </string> -->

	<string id="st_knifebf4">
        <text>The ЂOTs-04ї Combat knife (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_knifebf4_descr">
        <text>The OTs-04 knife was developed at the Tula Central Design Research Bureau (TsKIB) in the late 80s - early 90s and was intended for special forces of the Interior Ministry troops.</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_kukri">
        <text>Kukri (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_kukri_descr">
        <text>This is a special blade made of high-carbon steel with excellent cutting and chopping properties. Ideal for cutting mutants of all stripes, and for protection against them.</text>
		</string>

	<string id="st_tactical_knife">
		<text>Monolith's Blade (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tactical_knife_descr">
		<text>[RUSSIAN ACCENT "ON"] It is rumoured, these blades are produced in very a few by masters from a groupment Monolith. Threw composition of alloy not known - it is talked to extract him it is possible only in the heart of sarcophagus.[RUSSIAN ACCENT "OFF"]</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_tomahawk">
		<text>Gerber Downrange Tomahawk (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tomahawk_descr">
		<text>Tactical tomahawk, multi-tool and breaching tool, all-in-one solution.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 CQB (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration (military green colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup 5.56mm assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH&Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch). The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr "universal army rifle") was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units. CQB - has less weight and increased rate of fire compared to the original.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3 Commando (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - Army Universal Rifle) is an Austrian 5.56x45mm NATO bullpup assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr-Daimler-Puch and now manufactured by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG. The Steyr AUG A3 differs from the base model in the presence of four Picatinny slats: the top one is used for attaching sights, a grenade launcher or a vertical front handle can be attached to the bottom, and a laser pointer or other necessary additional equipment is attached to the side.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Trijicon Acog (x4) and PEQ LA5 LAM.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_howa20">
		<text>Howa Type 20 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_howa20_descr">
		<text>The Howa Type 20 Assault Rifle, referred to as the Type 20 5.56mm Rifle, is an ambidextrous assault rifle resistant to corrosion for exposure to seawater, developed for the Japan Ground Self-Defense Force by Howa. A small arms test was made by the JGSDF in 2018 to compare the HK416, SCAR-L, and Type 20. All three rifles satisfied the JGSDF's requirements of better environment durability, fire power and extensibility over the then-in-service Type 89, but the Type 20 received the highest score. It is speculated that the design was influenced by Japan's experience of procuring and utilizing a number of foreign rifles, and has been compared to the HK433 and the SCAR.\n
		The J-3 high-power cartridge, a 5.56 mm round made to be powerful enough to penetrate modern body armor despite the rifle's relatively short barrel length, was developed specifically for the Type 20.\n
		It remains a mystery why, how, and in what quantity this rifle came to the participants of a scientific expedition to the Zone.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: MARCH Shorty scope and AN/PEQ-15A DBAL-A2 Laser Device\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556">
		<text>Ruger SR-556 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_descr">
		<text>The SR-556 is a semi-automatic AR-15 style rifle manufactured by Sturm, Ruger & Co. The rifle was introduced in 2009 in .223 Remington/5.56?45mm NATO and as a .308 Winchester AR-10 variant in 2013, the SR-762. It is one of several AR-15 rifles to use a gas piston operation. Ruger announced on May 15, 2009 on the SR-556 being produced, and in January 2016, Ruger discontinued all existing SR-556 rifles in preparation for a new takedown variant.\n
		Several of these rifles came to the Zone through the scientists. According to rumors, six small containers with these guns were sent from foreign sponsors to Professor Sakharov, but 5 of them were lost before arrival.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for Picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_tac_siber">
		<text>SIG SG550 Tactical (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_tac_siber_descr">
		<text>Renowned for its high production quality and good performance, the SG 550 is often referred to as the finest 5.56 mm rifle ever made. It has a side-folding skeletonised buttstock and a lightweight aluminium bipod that folds into grooves in the lower handguard.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
	    %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Tactical handguard, Vertical grip, AN/PEQ-16 Laser Aim modul and Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for Picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight and 1P76 Rakurs (Picatinny).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor\n
	    %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_tac_siber">
		<text>SIG SG552 Tac Commando (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_tac_siber_descr">
		<text>The SG 552 Commando is designed for urban combat, making it the most compact member of SIG's renowned SG 550 family, which enhances its CQC capabilities.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
	    %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Vertical grip, AN/PEQ-16 Laser Aim modul and Tritium sights.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for Picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight and 1P76 Rakurs (Picatinny).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usp_tac">
        <text>HK USP Match Tactical (BaS)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_tac_descr">
        <text>This is a modification of the HK USP Match specially developed for scientists by personal order of Professor Sakhorov, designed for use in the "Specialist-Scientist" kit. The mechanism is improved with the use of artifacts; additionally, it allows the installation of a silencer and includes a set of extended magazines capable of holding 22.\n
		(The Specialist-Scientist kit includes: VSS Savant, HK USP Match Tactical, Monolith Blade).\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Laser Aiming Module and Red Dot Sights mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Gemtech suppressor</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_grenade_launcher">
		<text>GP-25 "Kostyor" grenade launcher (BaS+Van)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_descr">
		<text>A single shot, front loaded, rifled under-barrel grenade launcher for assault rifles made in Warsaw Pact countries. Designed to greatly expand fire-power of a basic infantry squad. The firing mechanism is self-cocking, with a manual safety catch and automatic shot prevention if incorrectly installed onto a rifle.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] muzzle velocity: %c[ui_gray_1]~76 m/sec\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] fire range: %c[ui_gray_1]~300 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] reload time: %c[ui_gray_1]slow\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ammunition: %c[ui_gray_1]VOG-25 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203">
		<text>M203 grenade launcher (BaS+Van)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203_descr">
		<text>A modified M203 grenade launcher whose length has been decreased by three inches, and which can be attached to weapons by means of a Picatinny rail. Thanks to a changed mount, this grenade launcher is widely used around the world and can be installed on most currently produced rifles. Although of more modern design, it has almost the same properties as its Soviet counterpart - the GP-25 grenade launcher.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] muzzle velocity: %c[ui_gray_1]~76 m/sec\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] fire range: %c[ui_gray_1]~300 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] reload time: %c[ui_gray_1]slow\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ammunition: %c[ui_gray_1]M203 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
