<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Ammunition
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="ammo_23x75_shrapnel">
		<text>"Shrapnel-25" 23x75mm (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_23x75_shrapnel_descr">
		<text>Cartridge with buckshot charge. Application range up to 25 meters. It is used for firing from the KS-23 carbine. Due to the fact that the barrel has rifling in the KS-23 carbine, the buckshot flies over a large area, which allows you to shoot offhand, practically without aiming.\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ammo_23x75_barrikada">
		<text>"Barrikada" 23x75ìì (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_23x75_barrikada_descr">
		<text>A cartridge with a steel pointed bullet. It is used to forcibly stop vehicles by damaging them. Application range up to 100 meters. It is used for firing from the KS-23 carbine.\n</text>
	</string>

<!--	 <string id="ammo_23_eco">
		<text>Ecolog-23 cartridge (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_23_eco_s">
		<text>Ecolog-23</text>
	</string> 
	<string id="ammo_23_eco_descr">
		<text>A special cartridge designed for the needs of the scientific staff located in the Zone. Depending on the task, it is filled with different types of solutions. Requires very careful handling. How to use: very slowly put into the weapon.\n \n%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armor class: %c[ui_gray_1]none\n%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]none\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Using a thin wolfram needle, it pierces the skin of the mutants to inject the solution.</text>
	</string> -->


	<string id="st_wpn_ks23">
		<text>KS-23 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_descr">
		<text>Special carbine, 23 mm - Soviet multi-functional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: The long 700mm barrel can be replaced by short 510mm one to decrease the weight of the weapon.\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban">
		<text>KS-23M Drozd (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_descr">
		<text>Shortened version of KS-23 with removable metal stock. 23 mm - Soviet multi-functional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: Boar Tactical Kit for KS-23M Drozd.\n</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up">
		<text>KS-23 Boar (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up_descr">
		<text>Shortened version with mounted Trijicon RMR reflex sight. 23 mm - Soviet multi-functional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery. Also this version has thread for sound suppressor that can be found somewere at south locations of Zone.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: KZRZP suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up">
		<text>KS-23 Short Barrel (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up_descr">
		<text>Special carbine, 23 mm - Soviet multi-functional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery. This modification of KS-23 has short 510mm barrel installed on it instead of standard long 700mm one.\n </text>
	</string>
	
<!-- 	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog">
		<text>ÊÑ-23 Ecolog (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog_descr">
		<text>Modification of KS-23, developed for the needs of the scientific staff located in the Zone.\n </text>
	</string> -->



	<string id="st_addon_scope_23_up">
		<text>510 mm Barrel for KS-23 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_23_up_descr">
		<text>
		%c[ui_gray_1]Short and light barrel for KS-23 Carabine. This upgrade is irreversible. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] KS-23 Carabine
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_kab_up">
		<text>Tactical Kit for KS-23 Drozd (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_kab_up_descr">
		<text>
		%c[ui_gray_1]The kit includes: Threaded barrel for using with suppressor and Trijicon RMR sight with mounting module. This upgrade is irreversible.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] Carabine KS-23M Drozd
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
</string_table>