<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc">
		<text>AK-74 PMC (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc_descr">
		<text>A modification of the Kalashnikov assault rifle, developed in 1970 for the 5.45x39 cartridge. It differs from the standard version by the installed body kit, which includes a tactical grip, a forend with picatinny rails and a folding telescopic buttstock, which significantly improves ergonomics of the gun. The kit also includes a laser targeting device, a tactical flashlight and an adapter mount for sighting devices.\n
		In the Zone similar models are usually used by mercenaries, Ukrainian special forces, various PMCs and other power structures for conducting special operations.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver and for Dovetail mount except of PSO scopes with eyecup, EOTS-62 and 1P59 Giperon.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: ATG suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac">
		<text>AKS-74U Tactical (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range.\n
		This special variant has a 45 round RPK magazine.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for dovetail mount (except of PSO scopes with eye cup and 1P59 Giperon) and all Red Dot Sights except of Aimpoint PRO and Aimpoint T1 with high mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-4 suppressor</text>
	</string>
</string_table>