<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_igi_ks23_ecolog">
		<text>KS-23 "Blowgun"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_igi_ks23_ecolog_descr">
		<text>Modified smoothbore carbine, multifunctional police weapon designed for crowd control, selective force, mental and chemical influence on offenders. The rifle is operated using sliding forend, which is rigidly connected to the improved bolt. Unlike the basic design the barrel is locked when fired by rotating the bolt. Trigger mechanism is of trigger-type. Ammunition is fed from three-round magazine, located below the barrel.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mass: %c[ui_gray_1]3,85 kg\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Length: %c[ui_gray_1]1040 mm\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barrel length: %c[ui_gray_1]510 mm\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Cartridge: %c[ui_gray_1]Dart\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Caliber: %c[ui_gray_1]23 mm\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Action: %c[ui_gray_1]Pump action\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Effective range: %c[ui_gray_1]up to 100 m\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Max. range: %c[ui_gray_1]150 m\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Feed system: %c[ui_gray_1]Underbarrel tube which holds 3 cartridges, plus one cartridge in the chamber\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Sight: %c[ui_gray_1]Integrated 3.4x scope\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo_23_igi_eco">
		<text>23x75 "Cloudkill" Cartridge</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_23_igi_eco_s">
		<text>23x75 Poison Cloud</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_23_eco_descr">
		<text>Special use cartridge developed by the Ecologist faction, part of an ongoing joint study with Duty. This cartridge contains a hollow metal ball filled with a liquid toxin derived from chemical anomalies. On impact with a target, the toxin vaporizes into a chemical cloud that severely weakens the targets and produces a similar effect on any nearby targets. Against all targets it induces lethargy and weakness, making them more susceptible to impacts and other forms of damage. With mutants specifically, the round weakens their ability to exert force, reducing the strength of their attacks. Specially ordered by Duty to increase the chances of surviving highly dangerous mutant raids by weakening the stronger monsters.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="igi_task_text_community_tracking_shot_name">
		<text>Beacon of Science</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_community_tracking_shot_about">
		<text>Young man, would you like to contribute to science? We are on the verge of a terrific discovery in the field of genetic research! We have the basic data to create the CHAZ Mutant Behaviorism Theory. In a nutshell: our research is based on the genetic information of the behavior of every living organism on the planet. That being said, yes, we have a job for you. You will have to travel out to a certain location and locate the mutant species we want. In addition, you will be issued registered equipment in the form of a special rifle with a telescopic sight and a few syringe darts to mark the target. Again, to mark, but not to kill. Upon completion of the assignment, you will be required to return the rifle and shells. Please note that this ammunition is not live ammunition. This is a valuable one-of-a-kind piece made to order at the ChAZ Research Institute and the distance of the shot is very important. So I have a convincing request to mark the targets at the longest possible distance, otherwise the capsule containing the substance may break and fail to mark the mutant organism.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_community_tracking_shot_text">
		<text>The chief of scientists gave me the job of shooting a special ammunition, giving me a rifle and special liquid darts. I am contractually obliged to move out according to the coordinates given to me. I need to mark a mutant species and try not to kill it. The chief added: The longer the distance of the shot, the more likely it is that the capsule inside the dart will remain intact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_community_tracking_shot_finish">
		<text>Good job, stalker.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
